

+88 01727244864



joyonto.karmakar.cse@gmail.com

github.com/Joyontokarmakar

joyontokarmakar.netlify.app

()

linkedin.com/in/joyontokarmakar

OBJECTIVES

I am a Front-end Developer and I love to do coding also I counted myself as a dedicated and hardworking person, I created lots of successful websites that are fast, easy to use, and built with my best try. I used HTML, CSS, CSS Framework and Library, JavaScript and JavaScript Framework also library and JavaScript wrapper and also to produce responsive websites and web apps that provide users the best and most appropriate experience suited to their device and browser.

SKILLS

Programming Language: JavaScript

Web Design: HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, SASS

Web Development: Vue JS, Nuxt JS, React JS, ES6

Project Management Tool: Clickup, Trello

Joyonto Karmakar

Front-end Web Developer

Version Controling Tool: Github, GitLab, Bit Bucket

Others: Postman

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER - (02/2021 - PRESENT)

JATRI SERVICES LIMITED - Dhaka, Bangladesh

RESPONSIBILITIES: Understanding of the web development process from inception to deployment, understanding of industry trends and the newest programming languages and the technical skills. Responsible for developing new user-facing features, determining the structure and design of web pages, building reusable codes, optimizing page loading times, and using a variety of markup languages to create the web pages.

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER (INTERN) - (07/2020 - 01/2021)

CODERSPY IT SOLUTIONS LIMITED – Dhaka, Bangladesh

RESPONSIBILITIES: Work closely with lead developers to design products and solutions to different user and infrastructure problems. Maintain standards compliance. Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability. Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders.

PROJECTS

BRTC ONLINE TICKETING WEBSITE

% LIVE SITE LINK: ticketing-brtc.gov.bd

TECHNOLOGY USE: Vue Js, Nuxt Js, Tailwind CSS.

DESCRIPTION: It's a Government project. I did all frontend design and localization part of this project with full responsive. This project has two functional sight. One is short distance route and another One is Intercity. User can buy BRTC Buses ticket from this website for all available route.

ONLINE TICKETING WEBSITE

% LIVE SITE LINK: brothersnavigation.com

TECHNOLOGY USE: Nuxt Js, Vue Js-2, Tailwind Css, Ssl-Commerze Payment Gateway.

DESCRIPTION: User Can Buy Their Launch Journey Ticket Through This Website. User No Need To Log In Here. User Can Pay By Ssl Commerze Payment Gateway. After Purchasing Successfully A Ticket User Can Print His/Her Ticket From The

CATERING SERVICE WEBSITE

% LIVE SITE LINK: mama-s-catering.web.app ✓

Code: </> Client side </> Server side </>

TECHNOLOGY USE: React JS, Node JS, React Bootstrap, Express JS, Mongo DB, Firebase.

■ **DESCRIPTION:** Admin can upload service and can make new admin and can update the ordered product status. User can choose and buy product from the product list. Amin and User both will be authenticate in this website by login systemSuccessfully A Ticket User Can Print His/Her Ticket From The Website.

EDUCATION

BSC IN CSE | SOUTHEAST UNIVERSITY

2017-2021 | Dhaka, Bangladesh | CGPA: 3.83

HIGHER SECONDERY | SHAHID SYED NAZRUL ISLAM COLLEGE

2013-2015 | Mymensingh, Bangladesh | GPA: 5.00

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

COMPLETE WEB DEVELOPMENT | PROGRAMMING HERO COMMUNITY

12/2020 - 03/2021

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN | CODERS TRUST BANGLADESH

09/2018 - 12/2018

TOP CONTRIBUTOR | GOOGLE CROWDSOURCE

08/2018

INTRA UNIVERSITY MATH OLYMPIAD (RANK-4TH) | SOUTHEAST UNIVERSITY

09/2017